YURII PANASIUK

<u>Software Developer</u>

+372 580 43 564



thoryur@gmail.com



Alasi 31, 50109 Tartu, Estonia



SUMMARY

Hello, I have been using Mestrelab products for many years, primarily Mnova, and I am impressed with Mnova Gears and, ELN.

In 2022, I initiated my study of Java to understand the functionality of ELN and prediction tools. In 2023, I enrolled in Kood/Jõhvi to acquire comprehensive and systematized knowledge about software development.

My aspiration is to work for Mestrelab because I genuinely believe it aligns with my dream job. In light of this, could you please provide feedback on the skills I should concentrate on, to apply for a Software Developer position in two years.

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Java, Go
- SQL, HTML, CSS
- Spring Boot, BootStrap
- Organic Chemistry

CERTIFICATIONS

- AWS Knowledge: Cloud Essentials
- Java 2 Agile Web
 Development JavaGuru
- Java 1 Intoduction to Java JavaGuru

EDUCATION

Ukrainian State Chemical Technology University

Master degree, Pharmacy and Technology Sep 2000 – Jul 2005

kood/Jõhvi

Software development 2023 - Present

EXPERIENCE

GitHub

https://github.com/Pomog/DBSCAN https://github.com/TartuDen/groupietracker

RnD Chemist

TBD Pharmatech | 2021 - Present

• Synthesis of organic molecules

Chemist, organic chemistry

Enamine Ltd. | 2012 - 2021

- Custom synthesis projects
- Synthesis of organic molecules
- Development of purification methods for synthesized compounds (scale from 10 mg to 100 g)

Pharmaceutical production engineer

Dnepropetrovsk State Biofactory | 2005 - 2012

• Veterinary Drugs Production